(Amy:)When did you get
an engagement ring?
(Sheldon:)My mother gave it to me,
(Sheldon:)and I had been thinking
about giving it to you,
(Sheldon:)but then we broke up.
(Meemaw:)Well, thank goodness
for that.
(Amy:)Sheldon, will you please tell
your grandmother
(Amy:)to stay out of this?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't think
I could do that.
(Meemaw:)Sheldon, tell this girl
(Meemaw:)that my ring will never be
on her finger.
(sighs) Y...
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna opt out
of that one, too.
(Amy:)Who said I even want
to be engaged to him?
And if I do, I-I don't need
your hand-me-downs!
All right, all right!
Look, l-let's all...
(Sheldon:)let's remain calm
and analyze this situation.
(Sheldon:)Now, I realize that
you've only known each other
(Sheldon:)for less than a day,
(Sheldon:)but is it possible this
crankiness is because
(Sheldon:)your cycles have synced?
(Meemaw:)You leave the room
(Meemaw:)and let the grown-ups talk.
(Penny:)Now.
(Amy:)Don't speak to him
like he's a child.
(Sheldon:)Thank you. I'm gonna go next
door and play with Leonard.